Class of 1930 Records, 1926-2000
Smith College Archives
Class of 1930 Records
1926-2000
Smith College. Class of 1930.
RG 80
15 boxes (9.8 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection contains photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1930.
Historical Note
The Class of 1930 was the fifty-second entering class and the fifty-second graduating class of Smith College.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Class of 1930 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1930, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, letters, questionnaires, and other memorabilia.
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1930 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- Addresses 1926-1930 (Box 2021, Folder 1)
- Class Baby 1931 (Box 2021, Folder 2)
- Baccalaureate Sunday 1930 (Box 2021, Folder 3)
- Clippings 1928-1930 (Box 2021, Folder 4)
- Commencement 1930 (Box 2021, Folder 5)
- Commencement Music 1930 (Box 2021, Folder 6)
- Commencement Photographs 1930 (Box 2021, Folder 7)
- Commencement Speaker 1930 (Box 2021, Folder 8)
- Fund Letters n.d. (Box 2021, Folder 9)
- Freshman Handbook 1926-1927 (Box 2021, Folder 10)
- Freshman Frolic 1926 (Box 2021, Folder 11)
- General n.d. (Box 2021, Folder 12)
- Groups 1926-1930 (Box 2021, Folder 13)
- Hoop Rolling 1930 (Box 2021, Folder 14)
- Ivy Day 1930 (Box 2021, Folder 15)
- Ivy Day Photographs 1930 (Box 2021, Folder 16)
- Junior Prom 1929 (Box 2021, Folder 17)
- Junior Prom-Garden Party 1929 (Box 2021, Folder 18)
- Junior Ushers 1929 (Box 2021, Folder 19)
- Last Chapel 1930 (Box 2021, Folder 20)
- Last Sing 1930 (Box 2021, Folder 21)
- Class Letters 1956-1967 (Box 2021, Folder 22)
- Class Letters 1970-2000 (Box 2021, Folder 23)
- Senior Dramatics 1930 (Box 2021, Folder 24)
- Senior Dramatics-Photographs 1930 (Box 2021, Folder 25)
- Senior Statistics 1930 (Box 2021, Folder 26)
- Songs 1926-1930 (Box 2021, Folder 27)
- Sophomore Carnival 1928 (Box 2021, Folder 28)
- Sophomore Push 1928 (Box 2021, Folder 29)
- Step Sing 1930 (Box 2021, Folder 30)
- Class Supper 1930 (Box 2021, Folder 31)
- Reunions-General n.d. (Box 2022, Folder 1)
- Reunions-Reunion Register 1931, 1935, 1940 (Box 2022, Folder 2)
- Reunions 1931 (Box 2022, Folder 3)
- Reunions 1935 (Box 2022, Folder 4)
- Reunions 1940 (Box 2022, Folder 5)
- Reunions 1945 (Box 2022, Folder 6)
- Reunions 1950 (Box 2022, Folder 7)
- Reunions 1955 (Box 2022, Folder 8)
- Reunions-Photographs 1955 (Box 2022, Folder 9)
- Reunions-Photographs 1955 (Box 2022, Folder 10)
- Reunions-Photographs 1955 (Box 2022, Folder 11)
- Reunions-Reunion Book 1955 (Box 2022, Folder 12)
- Reunions 1960 (Box 2023, Folder 1)
- Reunions 1960 (Box 2023, Folder 2)
- Reunions 1962 (Box 2023, Folder 3)
- Reunions 1965 (Box 2023, Folder 4)
- Reunions 1970 (Box 2023, Folder 5)
- Reunions 1973 (Box 2023, Folder 6)
- Reunions 1975 (Box 2023, Folder 7)
- Reunions 1980 (Box 2023, Folder 8)
- Reunions 1980 (Box 2023, Folder 9)
- Reunions 1985 (Box 2023, Folder 10)
- Reunions 1985 (Box 2023, Folder 11)
- Reunions 1990 (Box 2023, Folder 12)
- Reunions 1995 (Box 2023, Folder 13)
- Reunions 2000 (Box 2023, Folder 14)
- Reunions-Reunion Napkin with Cartoon n.d. (Box 2023, Folder 15)
- Reunions-Songs 1980, n.d. (Box 2023, Folder 16)
- Reunions-Questionnaire: Correspondence 1964-1965 (Box 2024, Folder 1)
- Reunions-Questionnaire: Tabulations and Report 1965 (Box 2024, Folder 2)
- Reunions-Questionnaire by Ely Chinoy 1965 (Box 2024, Folder 3)
- Reunions-Questionnaire by Ely Chinoy 1965 (Box 2024, Folder 4)
- Reunions-Questionnaire by Ely Chinoy 1965 (Box 2024, Folder 5)
- Reunions-Questionnaire by Ely Chinoy 1965 (Box 2024, Folder 6)
- Reunions-Questionnaire by Ely Chinoy 1965 (Box 2024, Folder 7)
- Reunions-Questionnaire by Ely Chinoy 1965 (Box 2024, Folder 8)
- Reunions-Questionnaire by Ely Chinoy 1965 (Box 2024, Folder 9)
- Reunions-Questionnaire by Ely Chinoy 1965 (Box 2024, Folder 10)
- Reunions-Questionnaire by Ely Chinoy 1965 (Box 2024, Folder 11)
- Scrapbook (Box OV)